One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Luffy and Whitebeard
Vmy heart feels like it's gonna burst!
Hey, partner! Can't you do anything?!
How is my wax power gonna help us here?!
Why are Luffy and the others falling from the sky?
To answer that, we must turn back the clock a little.
What was that?
The wave stopped!
What happened?!
What the hell is this?!
We're trapped in ice! Now we can't go anywhere at all!
The only one who could've done this is...
Take a look below. There's your answer.
Old Whitebeard...
The battle has already begun!
Listen up, you guys!
I've got an idea how we can get past this!
Now that we've made it this far, we have to hurry!
We've got less than three hours till they execute Ace!
Yeah, so?
What?!
He wants us to slide the ship down the frozen wave?
That's our only choice! First off, we have to break the ship out of the ice!
Are you an idiot?! This is a warship! It's not gonna move that easily!
That's right, you moron!
If we work together, I know we can do this!
I'm starting to feel like we really can...
That's right! We've got the man who's gonna conquer the world, Captain Buggy, on our side!
If the Captain says we can do it, then I know we can!
Calling all ships and troops.
Our target is site TOTTZ.
Change formation and initiate Operation Three.
It's a broadcast of the Navy's plans...
Make haste with the preparations.
TOT... What was that about?
Dunno... Probably some sort of code.
Once the preparations are complete, we'll push the schedule forward and execute Ace!
Over!
Luffy-kun...
Let's hurry!
Vwe can't wait any longer. There's no time to argue about this!
Everyone! Vwe're going with Straw Hat-boy's idea!
Go!
H-Hey!
Wrong way!
That brings us back to the present, where Luffy and the others are falling.
What happened?! Was that a warship falling out of the sky?!
It's water... We're saved.
We fell into the sea.
I thought we were gonna crash into the ice and die.
Why is there no ice in this one spot?
Climb up! Get higher!
This ain't nothing compared to the water torture in Hell!
I swear, these Devil Fruit users...
Ace!!!
Luffy!!!
I finally found you!
Hey! Is that...
Crocodile!
That's not who I meant! Who's that huge-faced guy?
Vi'd expect no less from the Navy's full force. They're not to be underestimated.
Get ready for me, world!
Ace! I'm here to save you!
We're all here to save you!
Garp! It's your damn family again!
Luffy!
Look! It's not only Straw Hat!
Jinbe! And even Ivankov from the Revolutionary Army!
And behind them is a horde of history's most notorious pirates!
They're the Impel Down escapees!
The man who everybody talks about. Straw Hat.
Straw... Hat...
What's he doing here?!
That's not his usual crew, is it?
Luffy! I am so glad you are safe!
You have to see this, Helmeppo-san!
What is it? Nothing is gonna surprise me anym-
Straw Hat!
And I heard he'd been imprisoned in Impel Down! He really is amazing!
That's one hell of a team he brought with him.
I didn't think I'd be seeing him again so soon.
Hey, that's the little brother Ace is always talking about.
Now we've got all the Warlords here, new and old!
And that's the troublemaker rookie, Straw Hat?
Smoker-san, look!
I know.
You're mine!
Straw Hat and Crocodile...
Why are they working together?
So that's him...
Not only is he the grandson of Garp the Hero...
he's also the son of the Revolutionary Dragon...
We'll have to eliminate him as well.
Of all the things you could have done, you joined forces with Straw Hat Luffy...
Is this your answer, Jinbe?!
That's right! I quit being a Warlord!
Any way you look at it, that's a strange team...
I seriously doubt they all have the same objective.
At least, not on this battlefield.
Where's Croco-boy?
Huh? Well, considering the situation...
There he is!
He's trying to beat me to it!
Crocodile is moving in on Whitebeard!
Old Man!
Long time no see, Whitebeard!
You never learn, do you?
So you already made preparations to fight me, huh?
Once you become wet, you can't turn into sand!
I honored our agreement and helped you get here.
Why are you defending Whitebeard?
So this old guy really is Whitebeard?
Then don't touch him!
Ace likes this old guy!
You're pretty good, Ace's brother.
Don't let him near the Old Man!
When a man as great as you came back from the
East Blue missing an arm, everyone was surprised.
What sort of enemy did you give it up to?
That left arm of yours.
I wagered it...
on the new era.
Kid... That straw hat of yours...
It looks a lot like the one Red Hair used to wear.
You know Shanks, old guy?
I'm holding it for Shanks.
Look at this, Old Man! This is my little brother!
Have you come to save your brother?
That's right!
Don't you understand what you're up against?!
Someone like you doesn't stand a chance here!
Shut up! That's not for you to decide!
I know perfectly well! You wanna be the Pirate King, don't you?!
But I'm going to be the Pirate King, not you!
You're pretty damn cheeky...
I won't show mercy if you slow me down, you spoiled brat!
I'm doing what I want to do!
I'm gonna save Ace myself!
H-He's...
standing up to Whitebeard!
Unbelievable!
I can execute every one of them, right, Sengoku-san?
Of course.
They're moving Ace's execution time up?
You're sure that's what they said?
After they finish some kind of preparations.
Then some code stuff I didn't really get.
Since you wanna save Ace, too, I thought I'd tell you!
I see. This is rather important news.
Sorry about before.
Don't worry about it.
Why are they having such a friendly chat?!
Right!
Ace, I'm coming now!
How is he so confident?!
Move it!
So that's Ace's little brother?
Don't get in the kid's way!
Third Division, start your assault!
We're going too.
Seriously?!
Fourteenth Division, clear his path!
Yes sir, Commander Jil!
Luffy...
Just one man's recklessness got them this riled up?
Regardless, this won't alter our plans.
Don't lose focus!
Proceed as instructed!
That Sengoku...
Now that he's up against pirates, there's no need to keep the old execution time?
These "preparations" he's planning must be the key.
Old Man!
According to a Navy transmission, they're going to accelerate Ace's execution.
Yeah, I heard.
We'll play right into their plans if we start panicking over this leaked information.
He's not sloppy. It's no accident.
Not coming from that man.
Shove through!
Light-speed kicks?!
Don't get carried away. I won't let you through that easily.
It's Admiral Kizaru!
It's you, from Sabaody!
The Celestial Dragons will be on my case if I let you get away again.
Straw Hat Luffy.
That Straw Hat guy's about to die!
Death Wink!
I want to turn back and go home now!
What, Captain Buggy?!
I can't believe what you're saying!
Huh?
You wanna turn the tables of this battle? Are you serious?!
Well, I...
Nothing less from the legendary crew!
He doesn't even flinch facing Admiral Kizaru!
Well, no...
You guys only hear what you want to hear!
Straw Hat-boy, are vyou alright?
That was close! Thanks, Iva-chan!
It is vmy mission to protect vyou from death!
Kizaru again!
Wait, no. That's...
Kuma!
That's the bear-guy who sent us all flying!
Rolling Aesthe!
Bartholomew Kuma!
This is terrible!
Even though he's standing over with the other Warlords,
he's shooting lasers at vme after all vwe've been through together?
How unlucky for you to bump into us.
Straw Hat. This is where it ends for you!
Huh... Who're you?
I'm Fullbody!
I still owe you from the floating restaurant Baratie!
Ah... the guy who got his ass kicked by Sanji.
Don't tell me you've forgotten these chakrams?
Aren't you that hypnotist from Usopp's village?
What are you doing here?
With the Navy's help, I've perfected...
Jango-sama's Hypnotism.
Two chakrams. Twice as effective.
With "One, Two, Jango" you will fall asleep.
One, two...
Jango!
What's going on here?
Hina disappointed.
You... I met you back in Alabasta!
I don't have any more time to waste with you guys!
I won't let you run.
Kimono Sleeve Cage!
Everything that passes through my body... is locked tight.
There it is, her signature phrase!
Now you shall be captivated by Madame Hina!
I've had enough of being in cages!
Gear Second
He's fast!
I couldn't see him!
Hina negligence.
Our negligence too.
Madame Hina has bound our bodies and our hearts.
Stop right there!
Every single one of these guys is strong!
Straw Hat!
His ability is impressive, as always.
That reminds me.
I should take his shadow once again, and bring Oars back to life with it.
Come out and play, zombie warriors!
Now, my minions, go and capture Straw Hat!
Moriah!
Another tough guy.
Have them back!
There's more!
Of course! This is a battlefield!
People dying simply adds to my zombie army!
Capture Straw Hat!
He's the culprit behind the prison break!
Keep it up!
Your opponents are all commissioned officers.
How far do you think you will get?
Luffy...
Keep away, Luffy!
You oughta know already!
You and I are both pirates!
You should be out sailing however you want!
Me, I have my own adventures!
Me, I have my own friends!
Ace...
You have no right to interfere with that!
A weakling like you coming to rescue me...
Move!
Do you think I'm gonna let that happen?!
That would be too humiliating.
Go back, Luffy! Why did you come?!
Please, Luffy...
I don't want to take you with me!
This is my failure.
I'm...
your brother!
Didn't ya know?
When you exchange sake cups, you become brothers.
From today onward, we are brothers!
Just then, he definitely said "brother"...
That means he is also Roger's...?
Ace's parents died after he was born!
There's no way he can have a younger brother!
Those stupid pirate "rules"...
I've never heard of them!
Don't you get it?
Go, my zombie minions!
S-Sea water?
Jinbe!
They're weak against salt.
Moriah, those zombies of yours...
Luffy-kun, leave the zombies to me.
I'm counting on you.
Knight of the Sea Jinbe!
Former member of the Seven Warlords...
What are you doing?
It's only one rookie... Don't let him dictate the entire war this way!
Out of my way!
I'll crush him!
That man will be a danger in the future.
He was raised with his sworn brother, Ace.
But his actual bloodline makes him the son of the Revolutionary, Dragon!
The Revolutionary Dragon?!
The son of the world's most fearsome criminal?!
And I know this person!
His papa's a big deal!
He's gone and said it.
Luffy-san...!
Luffy...
Knowing you're the child of a demon makes me...
So that's how it is?!
I get it now.
Bastard!
That solves the riddle from Loguetown.
That's why Dragon saved him...
Did you just hear that?
Dragon... The Dragon?!
Head Office! Head Office!
This is Sabaody Archipelago.
Big news!
T-Tell the world!
We mustn't let him live!
Take him down with everything we have!
Fine.
There's no point in hiding it anymore.
Luffy is already a notorious outlaw. This news won't make any difference now.
Raising them as brothers was a big mistake!
Ace!
Say whatever the hell you want!
I'm saving you, even if I die!
That kid.
Only Straw Hat could say that to him!
We're Ace's family!
Show us that you can save him!
Marco, don't let him die.
Roger that.
Luffy...